eoem.cc 2014-05-27

# Privacy Policy_Detail Info_Information_Apple iPhone Accessories, Samsung Accessories, Powerbank, Headphones and Earphones Wholesale from China!

  **Last modified: August 8, 2008**

At Eoem we recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Eoem Co.,LTD. or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies , In addition, where more detailed information is needed to explain our privacy practices, we post supplementary privacy notices to describe how particular services process personal information.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at

EOEM CO., LTD   
B3 7/F, Mirador Mansion 58 Nathan Road, Tsim Sha Tsui,Kowloon  
Hong Kong  

 **Information we collect and how we use it**

We offer a number of services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us, In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

  *  **Information you provide** – When you sign up for a Eoem Account that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For certain services, we also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services.

  *  **Log information** – When you access eoem services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
  *  **User communications** – When you send email to Us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

 **Choices for personal information**

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the specific service privacy notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the supplementary service privacy notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case we may not be able to provide those services to you.

 **Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to nopublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know in order to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal and state law standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.
